Hey guys welcome to another video, let me tell you another one with the two dump e secrets
or the crunch here from a window snitching, so there is a tool called the lassong.exe
and maybe some of some here this tool in different courses or it will be you might be using
this tool.
Now lassong is one of a powerful tool we can take we can extract our crunch here from
the machine, so you can get lassong, let me, yeah you can let get lassong from the lassong
course the sand releases in the EXE format, so this is the latest version 2.4.6 maybe if
you are seeing the course, I do not know which version will be published at that time,
if download the latest version which we have, which you have, okay, let us try it out,
so nothing there, so you need to execute that executable assigned at EXE, that is all,
it will be automatically gripping the hash them of users and a password, here you can
see the user, like user attacker, instead of user asking there and it did some various
functionalities like it did some scanning and it did not find any of the credentials, let
me give a help here, so let me run the modules, browser, I hope I just given a result
in between, so there my program failed up, let me read on that and it did not find any
of the credentials, let me try it out all, you can run different modules here, let me try
it out, right side, 0 password has been found, okay, but the problem is this tool has been
easily cached up by the EDRs and integrate platforms, because this hash values get blocked
there, already, but sometimes they are publishing a new version, sometime you can able
to bypass that kind of detections, that static base detections, so hope you, this tool
will be helpful for a little bit coincidental of the machine, yep, let's hop off and we'll
connect you in the next video, see you guys, bye bye.